https://www.espressocoffeeshop.com/privacy-policy

Espresso Coffee Shop ("us", "we", or "our") operates the
www.espressocoffeeshop.com website (hereinafter referred to as the
"Service").
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use,
and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices
you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy
for Espresso
Coffee Shop is based on the Privacy Policy Template from Privacy Policies.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the
Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in
accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy
Policy, the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as
in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from www.espressocoffeeshop.com
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain
personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or
identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may
include, but is not limited to:
Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and
used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as
your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser
type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time
and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device
identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an
anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a
website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are
beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to
improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate
when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you
may not be able to use some portions of our Service. You can learn more
how to manage cookies in the Browser Cookies Guide.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Espresso Coffee Shop uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to —
and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province,
country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection
laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside Italy and choose to provide information to
us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to
Italy and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Espresso Coffee Shop will take all steps reasonably necessary to
ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this
Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to
an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place
including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
Espresso Coffee Shop may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Espresso Coffee ShopTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no
method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic
storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable
means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute
security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our
Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to
perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our
Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform
these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it
for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google
that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected
to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with
other Google services. Google may use the collected data to
contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service
available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out
browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript
(ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google
Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by
us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that
third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy
of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content,
privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify
you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our
Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the
"effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any
changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are
posted on this page.Contact us
Should you need any information pls do not hesitate to contact our customer service:
Espresso Coffee Shop - Phone: +39-049-9904445. - Fax: +39-049-9904446
E-Mail: info@espressocoffeeshop.com
